Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings and Dom Baron Chant Recordings
Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings
- Miscellaneous recordings
  - Tapes
    - [unknown], hupka_0542; Probably Missa Solemnis; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0549; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0550; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0551; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0564; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0566; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0567; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0568; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0571; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0572; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0573; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0574; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0582; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0583; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0584; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0590; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0591; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0592; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0593; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0594; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0595; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0596; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0597; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0598; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0599; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0608; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0609; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0614; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0615; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0616; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0617; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0618; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0619; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0620; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0629; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0630; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], 12/14/1954; hupka_0632; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0674; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0675; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0680; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0688; Reel 1; [Benevoli Festmesse - Orazio Benevoli?]; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0689; Reel 2; [Benevoli Festmesse - Orazio Benevoli?]; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0692; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0698; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0699; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0700; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0701; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0702; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0703; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0704; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0705; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0706; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0707A; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0735; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0736; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0737; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0738; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0744; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0748; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0749; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0750; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0752; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0753; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0765; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0766; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0786; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - [unknown], hupka_0788; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Phonodiscs [in progress]